{
  "maxAnswerQuantity": 4,
  "multipleAnswers": false,
  "afterAnswerDelay": 100,
  "beforeNextLevelDelay": 100,
  "questions": [
      {
          "question": "How many countries are part of Scandinavia?",
          "answers": [
              "2",
              "3",
              "4",
              "5"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "price": 500

      },
      {
          "question": "Which animal has the largest eyes?",
          "answers": [
              "Elephant",
              "Giraffe",
              "Owl",
              "Ostrich"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "price": 1000
      },
      {
          "question": "Which human lung holds more air?",
          "answers": [
              "Left",
              "Right",
              "Same",
              "Individually"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "price": 2000
      },
      {
          "question": "Which of the Canary Islands is the largest?",
          "answers": [
              "Tenerife",
              "Lobos",
              "Alegranza",
              "Lanzarote"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0,
          "price": 4000
      },
      {
          "question": "Who wrote the Sistine Madonna?",
          "answers": [
              "Raphael Santi",
              "Michelangelo",
              "Leonardo da Vinci",
              "Sandro Botticelli"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0,
          "price": 8000
      },
      {
          "question": "How long is the equator?",
          "answers": [
              "17,240km",
              "40,075km",
              "30,075km",
              "38,890km"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "price": 16000
      },
      {
          "question": "What animal was the first parachutist?",
          "answers": [
              "Chicken",
              "Pig",
              "Dog",
              "Cat"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "price": 32000
      },
      {
          "question": "What kind of animals are used to guard grain storage facilities in the UK?",
          "answers": [
              "Cocks",
              "Pigs",
              "Cats",
              "Dogs"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2,
          "price": 64000
      },
      {
          "question": "In which country do the tarantella dance?",
          "answers": [
              "Spain",
              "Argentina",
              "France",
              "Italy"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "price": 125000
      },
      {
          "question": "Which creature has the largest brain in relation to the body?",
          "answers": [
              "Ant",
              "Blue whale",
              "Beaver",
              "Elephant"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0,
          "price": 250000
      },
      {
          "question": "What number means Roman XC?",
          "answers": [
              "190",
              "70",
              "90",
              "900"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2,
          "price": 500000
      },
      {
          "question": "Which of the American states has the largest area?",
          "answers": [
              "Texas",
              "Alaska",
              "Florida",
              "California"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1,
          "price": 1000000
      }
  ]
}
